Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Raya, let's go.
Lict and the reincarnated elves headed toward the royal capital.
Well, about that time.
Let's go pay the rest of our friends a visit, and then we'll wipe out all humankind.
All right! Go!
Asta and Yuna were making their way as well, to head off the invasion. But during their trip, they realized that their hometown of Hajj village was under attack, so they parted ways with Nozel and the others.
Stay back! It's our turn now!
Boys and plant magic, Zofnir's breath, and Zofnir's fingers for good measure.
Asta tried desperately to rid the priest of poison plant magic, and Zofnir's fingers for good measure.
Asta tried desperately to rid the priest of poison plant magic, but even with the help of the Demon Slayer Sword, the spell's effects appeared to be very difficult.
You're not done yet, you hear me?! Don't die! You can't do it!
You're not done yet, you hear me?!
Don't die! You can't die! You were supposed to stick around for a while to watch over us!
I'm an alien.
Asta tried desperately to rid the priest of poison plant magic, but even with the help of the Demon Slayer Sword, the spell's effects appeared impossible to reverse.
You're not done yet, you hear me?! Don't die! You can't die! We were supposed to stick around for a while to watch over us!
To see me through!
To see all of us through!
That sword...
It's his.
I saw it back at the Midnight Sun's hideout.
It must have slipped into my grimoire somehow.
Maybe if I use it...
I can...
The sword...
Let's...
MAN POWER!
MAN! HOT!
MONE!
MAN!
farercentury
Live!
Think that you would pass with us.
Here we go.
I know that sword. It's the same one that creepy guy had earlier.
That weapon. Why does he have it?
Oh, Asta. I'm scared.
Hey, what's going on here?
This sword's got tons more dark power flowing into it than the ones I used before.
Gotta stay focused.
I can't go against the flow. I need to take it in. Think like it's a part of my body.
Now.
What is this?
Look. The poison's disappearing.
Please. This has to work.
Father!
What? I'm alive? Or am I dreaming? I thought that this would be the end of me.
No. Asta made you all better. Yeah.
I was so worried. Wow, Asta, you really are amazing. You know that?
He's okay.
Oh, man. And this sword is crazy powerful. I can barely control the thing.
Wait, that's it. Maybe now that I have this, I can find a way to change everyone back to normal.
He managed to eradicate all of the poison's effects.
I don't believe it.
Focus on your opponent. Monozone.
Crescent Moonsickle! Four blades!
What? But why? And how?
You're under the same reincarnation spell as the rest of us.
So why is the will of your human host still in control?
And you? That blade belongs to Litt.
So how did it get into your filthy hands?
What's more, someone without any magic power shouldn't be able to wield it at all.
How is this possible?
Who are you, anyway?
You disgust me. You insufferable, putrid human garbage.
Oh, good. Now I can make it to Litt's wedding after all.
Don't tell me you're going to give him those freaky flowers as a present. That's a bad move.
What?
You don't think he would like them?
But they're pretty.
And they're not the poisonous kind, either.
They're lovely.
Litt!
And they have a special meaning.
Kindness dwells within.
They simply appear poisonous,
so elves and birds don't disturb them.
Since the insects know that,
to them, these flowers are a sanctuary.
Oh.
Between elves and humanity, it's the same thing.
We lack an understanding, so we avoid each other.
Tessia's going to enjoy these, too.
Thank you.
Sure, of course.
We tried to understand.
And they made it perfectly clear.
They were all monsters!
Humans.
I can never forgive you!
So stay out of our way or you're dead!
Wait, I've felt this before!
Humans!
He's not even trying to hold back his magic!
He can't control himself!
You're right.
His mana says it all.
The elf spirit inside him is crying out in pain.
Is it possible?
Are the elves asking for help?
Hey, Yuno!
Let's go, Asta!
He's turning into something that's not an elf at all.
We should set him free!
What's happening?
It looks like he just blocked Yuno's attack!
Nice, Yuno!
I made you a pass, Asta!
Now strike!
Aaaaaah!
They were all monsters!
Humans!
I can never forgive you!
So stay out of our way or you're dead!
Aaaaaah!
Humans!
He's not even trying to hold back his magic!
He can't control himself!
You're right.
His mana says it all.
The elf spirit inside him is crying out in pain.
Is it possible?
Are the elves asking for help?
Hey, Yuno!
Let's go, Asta!
He's turning into something that's not an elf at all!
We should set him free!
Aaaaaah!
I made you a pass, Asta!
Now strike!
Aaaaaah!
Did he undo the reincarnation magic?
Now that I have this sword, I can save them!
You know's the only reason we won, so you'd better say thank you!
Come on, I think I deserve a little credit too, right?
No, I definitely did 100% of the work.
All you did was hold the sword.
If you did 100%, then I must have done 500%!
Yeah, that isn't how math works.
Dummy.
Asta!
Yuno!
I thought he was gonna kill us, and then he showed up just in time to stop him.
You're so brave!
You were brave too, Nash, protecting the others like that.
Thank you for saving us!
That was scary!
Okay, okay, we get it. Now give Yuno some space!
Wow, look, she's so tiny and beautiful!
Yes, she's like a doll!
Look at this!
I'm trying to watch the outfit!
No!
Asta, you know.
Father, are you okay?
Of course. I'm a bit dizzy, but I'll survive.
The poison's fading from the other villagers as well.
We can't thank you enough for this.
What a blessing.
Both of you have grown up to be so strong.
I don't think you want to marry me now, Sister Love!
Order, creation, magic, holy fist of love!
Oops, I did that out of habit.
I didn't know how much I missed this!
Do it again, Sister!
Again?
What an idiot.
Hey, Yuno, your ears are all pointy now.
Yeah, they are!
That's right, which means the two of us match!
Now that that's over with,
do you two have any idea what's happening to the kingdom?
It's like a new crisis ensues
before we're able to recover from the last.
Well, we don't have a lot of time,
but we better explain.
Yeah.
Who knows when another resurrected elf
might attack this place.
Either way, no matter what it takes,
we'll keep this kingdom safe!
Your Majesty!
There's trouble!
Please, sir!
What's all the noise about?
You'd better have a good reason
for disturbing my beauty rest!
I apologize, my liege,
but we have an emergency!
There are several mages
attacking the royal capital as we speak!
Things of that nature
tend to be Julius' responsibility.
Actually, sir,
the Wizard King's gone missing.
We can't locate him anywhere!
The Magic Knight headquarters is in chaos!
Is that true?
His timing couldn't have been worse!
Then again,
I don't really mind.
What?
Because it's finally my turn
to have the spotlight!
It was always the same thing with Julius.
Every time I got a chance to shine,
he'd ruin it!
But for the first time ever,
I'm calling the shots!
What a great speech,
Your Majesty!
You're the greatest ruler ever!
Send out an urgent message
to all the Magic Knight captains!
I need them to assemble immediately!
Uh, that's already done.
Although, many of them
never even responded
to the message we sent.
In fact,
we've received word
that some of the Magic Knights
have betrayed us.
What did you say?
Apparently,
Longris has escaped from detainment,
and he appeared to be leading the rebellion
with the rest of the Golden Dawn
at his side!
Seems like our other reincarnated friends
have already gotten the party started.
It would be nice
if they'd save some fun for us,
but I won't count on it.
Well, can you blame them?
Even someone as calm as I am
couldn't resist slaughtering those humans.
Ha!
You may act calm,
but you looked pretty amped up
in that last fight.
But yeah,
I don't think I can hold back either.
We're the same!
Aren't we?
So we should be able
to talk things over.
Both sides are mad
because we lost someone we loved.
Sorry, kid.
But nobody's gonna stand
in our way anymore.
Those two should be awakening
any moment.
You might as well
throw in the towel.
I felt this enormous surge
of magic power,
and then it just disappeared.
That's true,
it was really intense.
But whatever it was,
I'm sure they're okay.
They promised they'd meet us
in the royal capital,
so all we can do
is trust them.
Yeah, we've got to give it
our best shot
for their sake.
Those two were sure
about their decision.
You should concentrate
on what you need
to do as well.
Got it!
And then we had to fight
against this super-strong
person named Lick.
Stop.
No one can understand
anything you're saying.
Can't you pick between
speaking and eating,
you big dumb pig?
We don't have time for both!
Are you okay there, Austin?
He's a better fighter now,
but he still hasn't
changed that much.
Let me see.
You said some of your
fellow magic knights
have been possessed
by elf spirits
who want to kill humans.
Is that correct?
I couldn't have said
it better myself!
I'm surprised
you understood that.
Well, naturally,
I did raise this kiddo
from when he was
just a baby.
Oh, I still can't believe
what a fine young man
harassed us grown into!
I mean, Yudo was always
great, but...
He sure cries a lot, doesn't he?
These are tears of joy,
I promise!
Excuse me?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Who the heck are you, weirdo?
You forgot me already?
I'm the one you just defeated.
You've rescued me from the elf
who was possessing my body,
remember?
My name is Digit Talus.
Is this what you're actually like?
Why would you say that?
Of course this is
what I'm actually like!
How did I get myself
into this mess?
Oh, I should probably mention
I'm a member
of the Purple Orcas.
As some already know,
our former captain
was involved in bribery
and other kinds of corruption.
So I was patrolling
the Forsaken Realm
looking for ways
to rebuild
our squad's reputation.
Wow!
Endangered horseface berries,
I don't believe it!
And this car
never a species
can be found
in any encyclopedia!
Who knew the Forsaken Realm
was such a treasuredrove
of rare plants
that you don't see
in the capital?
As I wandered
through the forest,
I ended up getting lost.
The next thing I knew,
I wasn't myself anymore.
And then I started
attacking the village.
I still don't know
what's going on.
I mean,
everything happened
so quickly!
Stop panicking.
although there's one thing
I do know.
That elf spirit
who took over my body,
whoever it was,
he didn't want this.
He didn't approve
of all this hatred
and violence.
It wasn't his choice.
Come on, you know.
We'll save everyone.
The elves
and the humans.
Yeah.
Wait,
you're leaving already?
Bet you just
got back home.
Please stay with us.
Yeah,
we want to hear
more stories.
Now, now,
try not to be selfish.
We'll miss these two,
but the kingdom
needs protection.
There are other people
in danger,
just like we were
tonight.
Okay.
Will you write
to us again soon?
Of course.
It's a promise.
You better work
on your handwriting,
though, Osta.
It's way too hard
to read.
And you have to swear
that you won't get killed
no matter what.
Right.
Bye, Gramps.
Sorry it was so short.
Gramps?
Where did that
little nickname come from?
I don't know.
I just like it.
Well, I don't,
so stop it.
I'm sorry,
but would it be alright
if I came along
with you?
Despite my demeanor,
I am a magic knight.
Yeah, come on.
Let's get going.
See you later!
We're gonna go
save the Clover Kingdom!
Osta!
Take care!
Thank you for all
the letters
and the money,
but nothing's better
than you coming home safe.
Be careful out there!
Sister!
I love you so much!
Shut up!
You're off
to save the kingdom,
eh?
Our little Osta,
who's never been able
to use magic at all.
And you know,
he's the hope
of Hajj Village now,
even though he always
used to be so timid
and burst into tears
so easily.
You both grew up
so quickly!
It's unbelievable!
Take care of yourselves,
you hear?
Ah!
What's up with that
giant rock in the sky?
Oh boy,
I think it's finally
time for me
to have some fun
for real!
Answer all that,
we're super behind!
We should hurry!
I sense elven magic
up ahead.
It's coming from
the north and the south.
It's just a guess,
but maybe
even more magic knights
got possessed
and started attacking humans.
What should we do?
Aren't we supposed
to go to the capital now?
Even if they live out here,
they're still citizens
of the Clover Kingdom!
That's that then.
Since there are two places
in danger,
perhaps we should split up?
Good idea.
That way we can
protect everybody.
You go with Yuno!
No, I'll be fine
on my own.
Go with Asta.
Duh, Yuno is a whole lot
more kiggler-goo
than you are,
sword boy!
I don't need any backup,
so why don't you
just take him with you?
No, thanks.
Come on!
Take him!
Um, this is awkward.
Please don't fight
over me, okay?
No, you!
Look, I've got this,
which means I can turn
our friends back
to their regular selves.
And you don't have
that ability,
so it'll be better
if you bring somebody
with you to help out!
Surprisingly,
you're right.
Why is it surprising?
I guess he can use
his poison to incapacitate them.
I'm starting to feel
like you guys
don't want me here.
Ready?
Of course.
See you at the capital!
Let's go!
次の道への地図は
See you next time.